Promises are an incredibly powerful addition to the language,
التعهدات هي إضافة قوية جدًا إلى اللغة،
and a ton of both existing and future changes make use of them.
ومقدارًا كبيرًا من التغييرات الحالية والمستقبلية لتحقيق أقصى استفادة منها.
So being able to work with and write JavaScript promises is vital.
لذلك فإن القدرة على التعامل مع تعهدات JavaScript وكتابته أصبحت أمرًا ضروريًا.
They're so important, we've actually created
إنها مهمة جدًا، لذلك صممنا في الواقع
a standalone course dedicated to just JavaScript Promises.
دورة تدريبية مستقلة خاصة بتعهدات JavaScript فقط.
Hang on a second. Hey Cameron.
يُرجى الانتظار لثانية. مرحبًا كاميرون.
Hey Richard. It's good to see you.
مرحبًا ريتشارد. تسرني رؤيتك.
We were talking about JavaScript Promises and we told
سنتحدث عن تعهدات JavaScript لقد أبلغناهم
them about our dedicated course on JavaScript Promises,
بدورتنا التدريبية المخصصة لتعهدات JavaScript،
and we thought, did you want to talk about that a little bit?
وعن آرائنا، هل ترغب في التحدث قليلًا عن ذلك؟
I made a course on Promises – they're awesome – and you should go take it.
لقد قدمت دورة تدريبة عن التعهدات، إنها حقًا مذهلة، يجب أن تطلع عليها.
And the reason is is that Promises make it so much easier to do asynchronous code.
والسبب وراء ذلك أن التعهدات تجعل عملية إنشاء كود غير متزامن سهلة جدًا.
With Promises, your code's going to be easier to read, easier to write,
تُستخدم التعهدات لتسهيل قراءة الأكواد وكتابتها،
and most importantly as you all know,
والأهم من ذلك كما تعلمون إنها تجعل عملية،
it's gonna be a lot easier to debug.
إصلاح أخطاء الأكواد أسهل بكثير.
And while you're working on this class,
بينما تعمل في هذه الفئة،
you'll be also building an app called the Exoplanet Explore.
ستعمل أيضًا على إنشاء تطبيق يسمى مستكشف بيانات الكواكب خارج المجموعة الشمسية.
This is a really cool app because it helps people learn about
إنه تطبيق رائع حقًا لأنه يساعد الأشخاص في معرفة الكثير عن
planets around other stars in our galaxy, real planets.
الكواكب الموجودة حول النجوم في مجرتنا، أي الكواكب الحقيقية.
So it's really amazing and it's really fun and you
إنه تطبيق رائع وممتع حقًا
should definitely check out the course if you want to master Promises.
وعليك دراسة الدورة جيدًا إذا كنت ترغب في إتقان التعهدات.
You'll find a link to the course below.
ستعثر على ارتباط الانتقال إلى الدورة أدناه.